Tony Zhu

10324 Ember Glen Dr, Austin, Texas 78726 | 512-925-6961 | tonyzhu3141@gmail.com snickerton.github.io | linkedin.com/in/tonyzhu3141 | github.com/snickerton

Summary

Produces elegant yet efficient code with 5+ years of experience in programming.

Known as a proactive worker and team player with clear-cut, comprehensive communication.

Always passionate and enthusiastic about problem solving and working with technology.

Skills

Languages: Fluent in Java | experienced in HTML/CSS & Javascript | C#, Python, and C++

Tools: Unity, Agile/Scrum Methodology, Github, Keras/Tensorflow, Linux, Matlab.

Miscellaneous: Ideation Process, Rapid Prototyping, Public Speaking, Video Editing, Ultimate Frisbee.

Experience

Software Engineer Intern, Schneider Electric | June 2018 - August 2018

Microsoft HoloLens app to showcase a variety of Schneider products in AR. Development process includes extensive use of Unity, C# scripting, Visual Studio (Team Services), 3D modeling, and Agile workflow.

Intern, Cycorp Al | June 2016 - August 2016

Debugged and tested software products in a Scrum/Agile workflow environment.

Programmed high level software in C# and CycL for company projects and products.

Software Developer, A&M University VR Research | December 2017 - present

Hired onto graduate research project to develop virtual reality software in Unity: a VR application that displays stress points, fractures, and simulations of 3D objects from the software Abaqus.

Research Assistant, Deep Learning Lab | Nov. 2017 - present

Weekly topics and challenges on neural networks (Keras/Tensorflow in Python) assigned and supervised by Dr. Anxiao Jiang. Recent challenges involve a MNIST recognizer and a chatbot (NLP processing) by neural networks.

Education

Texas A&M University, College Station, TX

BS in Computer Science | University Honors

Class of 2021

Phillips Exeter Academy, Exeter, NH

David T. Swift Proctor Award

Class of 2017

Activities

Aggie Coding Club [Project: Tensorflow Snake] | Sept. 2017 - present

Active Member - Work in groups of 4-5 on an extensive long-term coding project. Current project involves training a neural network to beat the game Snake. In addition, attend lectures weekly provided by external companies/professionals regarding all things Code (e.g. Git, Docker, Types of Machine Learning). 3 hrs/wk

Texas A&M Coding Society | Sept. 2017 - present

Active Member - Attend socials, networking events, lectures by industry professionals or professors, and presentations of local projects. 1 hrs/wk

Aggie Artificial Intelligence Society | Sept. 2017 - present

Active Member - Attend demonstrations/workshops provided by external parties regarding AI and Machine Learning related topics. 1.5 hrs/wk